Guide to the Graduate School Reference Collection, 1958-ongoing
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Graduate School Reference collection 1958-ongoing
University Archives, Duke University
Duke University. University Archives
0.7 Linear Feet approx. 300 Items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Graduate School Reference Collection was compiled from a variety of sources by the University Archives for use in reference and research.
Collection Overview
The Graduate School Reference Collection was compiled from a variety of sources by the University Archives for use in reference and research. It includes printed matter, clippings, newsletters, reports, memoranda, and statistics. The collection ranges in date from 1958-ongoing.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Duke University. Graduate School
Duke University -- History -- 20th century
Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.)
Related Material
Graduate School Records, 1924-2004
Duke University Archives
Nicholas School of the Environment Reference Collection
Duke University Archives.
School of Engineering Reference Collection
Duke University Archives
Departments and Academic Divisions Reference Collection
Duke University Archives
Contents of Collection
- Container List
  - Clippings, 1963-ongoing (Box 1)
  - Graduate Student Affairs - Publications, 2000
  - Graduate School Report, newsletter, 1969-1972
  - Health Administration, 1975-1980
  - Master of Arts in Liberal Studies, 1980s-1990s
  - Microbiology and Immunology, 1972
  - Reports and Memoranda, 1958-ongoing
  - Roundtable on Science and Public Affairs, 1978-1986
  - Statistics, 1970s-1980s